export const quiz = {
	totalQuestions: 20,
	questions: [
		{
			id: 1,
			question:
				'A person who manages customers` money effectively and profitably.',
			answers: ['A seller', 'A banker', 'An architect'],
			correctAnswer: 'A banker',
		},
		{
			id: 2,
			question:
				'A person who plans, designs, and oversees the construction of buildings',
			answers: ['A seller', 'A banker', 'An architect'],
			correctAnswer: 'An architect',
		},
		{
			id: 3,
			question: 'To look after people when they are sick.',
			answers: ['A nurse', 'A banker', 'A teacher'],
			correctAnswer: 'A nurse',
		},
		{
			id: 4,
			question: 'A person who develops websites for clients.',
			answers: ['A nurse', 'An IT programmer', 'A teacher'],
			correctAnswer: 'An IT programmer',
		},
		{
			id: 5,
			question: 'A university academic of the highest rank.',
			answers: ['A nurse', 'An IT programmer', 'A professor'],
			correctAnswer: 'A professor',
		},
		{
			id: 6,
			question:
				'A person whose job is to keep, inspect, and analyze financial accounts.',
			answers: ['A nurse', 'An IT programmer', 'An accountant'],
			correctAnswer: 'An accountant',
		},
		{
			id: 7,
			question:
				'A person whose job involves selling and renting out buildings and land for clients.',
			answers: ['An estate agent', 'An IT programmer', 'An accountant'],
			correctAnswer: 'An estate agent',
		},
		{
			id: 8,
			question:
				'A person whose job involves helping people to sort out their legal affairs.',
			answers: ['An estate agent', 'A lawyer', 'An accountant'],
			correctAnswer: 'A lawyer',
		},
		{
			id: 9,
			question: 'I investigate and write articles to newspapers',
			answers: ['An estate agent', 'A lawyer', 'A journalist'],
			correctAnswer: 'A journalist',
		},
		{
			id: 10,
			question:
				'A medical practitioner specializing in children and their diseases.',
			answers: ['An estate agent', 'A pediatrician', 'A journalist'],
			correctAnswer: 'A pediatrician',
		},
		{
			id: 11,
			question: 'Plastic makes rivers and oceans dirty.',
			answers: ['True', 'False'],
			correctAnswer: 'True',
		},
		{
			id: 12,
			question: 'It doesn’t kill animals.',
			answers: ['True', 'False'],
			correctAnswer: 'False',
		},
		{
			id: 13,
			question: 'It takes one year to disappear.',
			answers: ['True', 'False'],
			correctAnswer: 'False',
		},
		{
			id: 14,
			question: 'A lot of companies want to replace plastic.',
			answers: ['True', 'False'],
			correctAnswer: 'True',
		},
		{
			id: 15,
			question: 'McDonald’s is trying to make a paper bottle.',
			answers: ['True', 'False'],
			correctAnswer: 'False',
		},
		{
			id: 16,
			question: 'Coca-Cola was world’s biggest plastic polluter in 2019.',
			answers: ['True', 'False'],
			correctAnswer: 'True',
		},
		{
			id: 17,
			question: 'Their aim is to create a paper bottle.',
			answers: ['True', 'False'],
			correctAnswer: 'True',
		},
		{
			id: 18,
			question: 'A paper bottle doesn’t open up a whole new world of packaging',
			answers: ['True', 'False'],
			correctAnswer: 'False',
		},
		{
			id: 19,
			question:
				'Coca –Cola wants to use only packaging from renewable sources.',
			answers: ['True', 'False'],
			correctAnswer: 'True',
		},
		{
			id: 20,
			question: 'They wouldn’t be good for our planet.',
			answers: ['True', 'False'],
			correctAnswer: 'False',
		},
	],
}
